

GEORGE-BOGDAN **PAUN**

Software Developer

About Me

Passionate software developer focused on frontend (React, Figma) while maintaining strong backend knowledge (Python) for efficient solutions. Proactive, solution-oriented, and adaptable to modern technologies.

- +40 760 056 651
- paunbogdan2@gmail.com

Bucharest

Language

- Romanian (nativ)
- English

Skills

Python

Figma

React.js

Matlab OOP

Jira

Expertise

- Problem Solving
- Creativity
- Agile & Task Management
- Data Processing & Backend (Dask, Polars)

Experience

Software Developer Bertrandt-Bucharest 2022 - Present

Valuable experience in a collaborative environment, where I developed my skills in both backend (Python, Polars, Dask, Flask) and frontend (Figma). Gained practical experience in task management using Jira and Agile workflows, contributing to component implementation and UI design. An ideal setting for professional growth at the start of my career.

Game Tester Electronic Arts - Bucharest 2018 - 2018 & 2019 - 2019

Game testing (specific parts of the game) and reporting visual, audio, and control-related bugs.

Reproducing errors to verify if they were fixed.

Achievements: Contributed to eliminating bugs in new versions of APEX before release.

Worked during the summer in both periods.

Education

University Politehnica of Bucharest

Faculty of Power Engineering - Industrial Informatics 2017 - 2021

High School Diploma

National College "Zinca Golescu", Mathematics - Informatics 2013 - 2017